International Brotherhood of Longshoremen Local 109 Records 6170
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Longshoremen Local 109 Records
1917- 2003
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Brotherhood of Longshoremen Local 109
6170
3.5 cubic feet
3.5 linear ft.
Reocrds, minutes.
5830491
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 13, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 19, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
5830491
- Meeting Minutes 1933-1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Installment on Insurance 1965-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Meeting Minutes 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Meeting Minutes 1954-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Drawing for Applications (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Insurance 1936-1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Installment 1936-1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Meeting Minutes 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- S. E. Ledger 1977-1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Daily Receipts, Duplicate of Quarterly Audits, Copy of Adjustment in Cash-Box 1966-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Meeting Minutes 1944-1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Expenses 1961-1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Office Book 1937-1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1932-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Minutes of All Meetings, Constitutions, Resolutions 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook 1969-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Scrapbook 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- End of an Era (compact disc) 2003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Agreements and Constitutions of other unions (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Working Rules (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Constitution and By-Laws 1959-1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Agreements 1917-1929 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Agreements 1930-1939 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Agreements 1940-1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Agreements 1950-1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Agreements 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Agreements 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Ledger 1941-1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)